(
"ai_sub_version": "3.4.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T06:11:42.720347",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
※この配信は演出により激しく点滅する場面がございます。部屋を明るくし画面から十分離れてご視聴ください。
*This stream contains scenes with intense flashing lights. Please watch in a bright room and stay at a safe distance from the screen.
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Welcome! Welcome!
本日はお忙しい中 数ある配信の中から当配信 兎田ぺこら7周年ライブをご指名いただき ご閲覧いただき 誠にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for taking time out of your busy schedule to tune in to Usada Pekora's 7th Anniversary Live today!
日頃のご愛顧にお応えいたしまして 兎田ぺこらオリジナルのステージを取り揃えましてのお出迎え お祭り騒ぎでゲストもたくさんでお送りいたします！
To show our gratitude for your support, we've prepared a special original stage, packed with festive fun and lots of guest stars!
玉の方もメダルの方も 全て超超超おすすめでお出迎えとなっておりますれば どちらのお客様も最後までジャンジャンバリバリとお楽しみくださいませ！
Whether you're aiming for the pachinko balls or slot medals, everything comes highly recommended, so please enjoy to your heart's content until the very end!
日頃ご自慢の右腕、左腕により一層の磨きをかけましてで しっかりとがっちりとコメントもしていってくださいませ！
Warm up your right and left arm and make sure to leave plenty of comments!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you very much!
いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
本日もさまざまな景... グッズをご用意しております！
Today, we also have various prize... merchandise available!
ぜひ本日のライブの思い出におひとついかがでしょうか？
How about getting one as a souvenir for today's live stream?
1つ目の目玉商品は、こちら！
Our first featured product is this!
アクリルパネル！
Acrylic Panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishのイナちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
This was actually drawn by Ina-chan from Hololive English!
とってもレア！とってもレア！そして、可愛いぺこらをありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Super rare! Super rare! And thank you for such a cute Pekora! Thank you so much!
イナ、ありがとうイナ！
Ina, thank you, Ina!
ぜひとも皆さんのデスクトップのお隣に置くといいぺこですね！
It'd be great to place it right next to your desktop, peko!
2つ目は、こちら！
The second item is this!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！イラストは、まるえり先生に描いてもらいました！
Random Acrylic Keychain! The illustration was drawn by Marueri-sensei!
めちゃめちゃ可愛いぺこですね！
It's super duper cute, peko!
ぜひとも全種揃えたくなってしまう、そんなランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
A random acrylic keychain that makes you want to collect all of them!
誰がくるかは届いてからのお楽しみぺこです！
Which one you get is a surprise until it arrives, peko!
3つ目は、ぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ...」Tシャツ！
The third item is the "Uso Peko Desho..." T-shirt with Pekora's handwritten text!
この暑い夏を乗り切るのにぴったりなTシャツ！
A T-shirt that's perfect for surviving this hot summer!
「うそぺこでしょ...」の場面がきっとある！そんな時に着たいTシャツぺこですね！
There will surely be moments where you go "Uso peko desho..."! That's the T-shirt you want to wear then, peko!
4つ目は、トラックジャケット！
The fourth item is a Track Jacket!
こちらもまた最高にかっこいいぺこですね！
This one is also super cool, peko!
後ろには、キービジュアルのぺこら！
On the back is the key visual Pekora!
この中に「うそぺこでしょ」Tシャツ、そしてジャケットを羽織って外に行ったら、最高～！
If you wear the "Uso Peko Desho" T-shirt under this jacket and go outside, it'd be awesome~!
お出かけにもちょうどいいぺこですね！
It's perfect for going out, peko!
そしてなんと、なんと！フルセットをご購入の方には、さらなる特典がございます！
And what's more, for those who purchase the Full Set, there's an extra bonus!
こちら！
Right here!
数量限定で、ぺこらの直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードが付いてくる！
In limited quantities, it comes with a postcard featuring Pekora's handwritten signature and foil-stamped message!
以上！ぜひ皆様、ジャンジャンバリバリゲットしてください！
That's all! Everyone, please go ahead and grab yours!
兎田ぺこらに夢と希望と未来を乗せまして、
With dreams, hope, and the future riding on Usada Pekora,
配信終了のお声がかかりますまで、
until we hear the announcement for the end of the stream,
一気にジャンジャンバリバリと、最終最後のお時間までご視聴くださいませ！
please keep watching enthusiastically all the way until the very end!
Ah 潮風に誘われて
Ah, invited by the sea breeze,
はしゃぐ声 波の音 近づいてゆく
cheerful voices and the sound of waves draw closer.
Ah 高い空 白い雲
Ah, high sky and white clouds,
まぶしい海と恋の季節
the dazzling sea and the season of love.
日に焼けた あなたが笑っていた
Sun-tanned, you were smiling,
たくさんの光がキラキラ
so many lights glittering brightly.
コイするココロで変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
With a heart in love, it starts to change—Lucky Day.
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our holding hands fall under a spell.
笑ってばかり ここは夏の国
Full of laughter, this is a summer paradise.
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrading myself!
Ah 照らし出す太陽が
Ah, the shining sun...
まぶしくてかき氷 イチゴ選んで
It's so dazzling; picking strawberry shaved ice.
Ah 青い空 白い砂
Ah, blue sky and white sand,
コントラストなピンクのくち
contrasting pink lips.
染まってく くちびる 照れ笑い
Stained lips, a bashful smile,
誘ってるみたいで ドキドキ
as if inviting me, making my heart flutter.
コイするココロがスピードあげてく
A heart in love keeps speeding up...
コイする ココロが スピードあげてく
My in-love heart is speeding up
見つめる ヒトミが 大胆になるよ
As we gaze, my eyes become bold
言葉はいらない 今を感じたい
No words are needed, I just want to feel the present
私をバージョンアップ！
Version up myself!
夕陽を映す海は オレンジ
The sea reflecting the setting sun is orange
二人のシルエット
Our two silhouettes
足をさらう星の砂
Star sand washing over our feet
そっと、ねぇ 連れてって遠くに
Softly, hey, take me far away
コイする ココロは もう止まらない！
My in-love heart can no longer be stopped!
合わせた手のひら 合図を送るよ
Joined palms send out a signal
何もいらない ふたりだけの国
I need nothing, in a world just for the two of us
私をバージョンアップ！
Version up myself!
コイする ココロで 変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
With a heart in love, a lucky day begins to change
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our held hands are falling under a spell
笑ってばっかり ここは夏の国
Nothing but smiles, this is a summer nation
私をバージョンアップ！
Version up myself!
私のブランニュー・デイ！！！
My brand new day!
イェイ！
Yay!
はい、みんな！ぺこらのライブに来てくれて、アリぺこでした！
Hi everyone! Thank you so much for coming to Pekora's live!
1曲目は『私をバージョンアップ！』でした！
The first song was "Watashi wo Version Up!"
1曲目当てた人いますか？
Did anyone guess the first song right?
何のね、曲が来るかみんなね、たくさん考えてくれたと思うけど、まずは1曲目は『私をバージョンアップ！』でした！
I think everyone was guessing what song would come first, but it was "Watashi wo Version Up!"
ということで、今回も兎田ぺこらパチンコスロットライブ第3弾！
So, this is the 3rd Usada Pekora Pachinko Slot Live!
「おいおい、ぺこちゃん。前回も前々回もパチンコスロットライブだったじゃん。なんで3回目もやるんだよ」って思いましたよね？
I'm sure you thought, "Hey Pekora, the last two were Pachinko Slot Lives! Why a third one?"
はい、わたくしも3回目はやりすぎか、さすがにやりすぎてるぺこなのかなって思いましたけども、こちら見てください！
Yes, I also wondered if doing a third one might be overdoing it, but take a look at this!
はい、兎田ぺこら7周年記念ライブということで、
Yes, as this is Usada Pekora's 7th Anniversary Live...
「7」なんです！
It's "7"!
「7」と言ったらやるしかないよね！そうぺこだよね！ということで、
When it's "7", we have to do it! Right, peko? So,
今回もやらせてください！めちゃめちゃね、いい曲たくさんあるぺこですので、絶対みんな楽しんでもらえる！
Please let me do it again! There are so many great songs, so I know you'll all enjoy it!
それだけは自信があるぺこですので、ぜひともお楽しみに！
I'm confident about that, peko, so please look forward to it!
そして、ハッシュタグのね「#兎田ぺこら7周年記念LIVE」でたくさん呟いてください！
And please tweet a lot using the hashtag "#UsadaPekora7thAnniversaryLIVE"!
ということで、ここからはみんなお楽しみのゲストパート！
And now, it's time for the guest part everyone's been waiting for!
今年はどんなお相手が来るのか、お楽しみに！
Please look forward to seeing who will join me this year!
兎神拳に二対一の戦いはない！
There is no two-on-one battle in Usagishinken!
覇王はこのケーオーただ一人！
There is only one Overlord, and that is this KO!
北兎無双！
Hokuto Musou!
静寂の闇を 溶かす瞬き
A twinkling light that dissolves the silent darkness,
星座のStory 語りかければ
when the story of the constellations speaks to us,
それぞれの思い 弾かれるように
as if triggered by our respective thoughts,
男たちの旅は始まる
the journey of men begins.
渇き果てて ひび割れてく時代で
In an era parched dry and cracking apart,
たった一つの 信じるものを追い求めてく
searching for the one single thing to believe in.
輝くDestiny star 導かれて 野望の果てまで
Guided by the shining Destiny Star, to the ends of ambition,
譲れない願い 向き合う時 運命始まる
when unyielding wishes confront each other, destiny begins.
数えきれない 悲しみを見つめ
Staring into countless sorrows,
光放つDestiny star
the Destiny Star emits its light.
いつも予言には 「答え」しかない
Prophecies always contain nothing but "answers",
辿る道は 自分次第で
but the path you walk depends on yourself.
進むべき明日を 切り拓くよう
To carve out the tomorrow we ought to head toward,
男たちは戦い続ける
men continue to fight.
命さえも 投げ出しても構わない
I wouldn't care even if I were to throw away my life,
そう思えるほど 守りたいもの見つけたから
because I've found something I want to protect that much.
ささやくDestiny star 迷いすてて 悪夢の果てまで
The whispering Destiny Star, casting away doubts, to the ends of the nightmare,
一歩も引けない プライドから 火花が飛び散る
sparks fly from a pride that refuses to yield even a single step.
まだ遠くても その手を伸ばして
Even if it's still far away, reach out your hand,
つかまえてよDestiny star
and catch it, Destiny Star.
絆確かめ 未来の扉 開けて飛び立つ
Confirming our bond, opening the door to the future and taking flight,
輝くDestiny star 導かれて 野望の果てまで
guided by the shining Destiny Star, to the ends of ambition,
譲れない願い 向き合う時 運命始まる
when unyielding wishes confront each other, destiny begins.
数えきれない 悲しみを見つめ 光放つDestiny star
Staring into countless sorrows, the Destiny Star emits its light,
Destiny star
チャンスぺこ！
Chance peko!
激熱ぺこ！！！
Super hot peko!!!
ここまじゃ ぺこの助
This is as far as you go, Pekonosuke!
怨みに歪んだ剣で ぺこーらは打てぬぺこよ！
You can't defeat Pekora with a sword twisted by grudge, peko!
紅い 雫滲む唇に
On lips stained with crimson drops,
ふわり 嘆きの霧触れてゆく
a mist of grief softly brushes by.
空に 浮かぶ鏡美しく
The mirror floating in the sky is beautiful,
遥か 暗夜の彼方照らしてる
illuminating the distant dark night.
降り注ぐ 数多の星に想い馳せて
Thinking of the countless pouring stars,
しめやかに 深い絆の血
quietly, a deep blood bond...
しめやかに深い絆の糸
The quiet, deep thread of blood bonds
強く強く結ぶ
Binds us tightly, tightly
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Those brightly shining azure eyes
闇よりの使いに 閉ざされても
Though locked away by an agent of darkness
繋いだ夢の橋 誰も奪えないから
No one can take away this bridge of connected dreams
無限の明日映して
Reflecting an infinite tomorrow
妖し光放つ鳴神に
Narukami shines with a bewitching light
甘い言葉の蜜香り立つ
Giving off the sweet honey scent of words
密か黒い鼓翼忍び寄る
Secretly drawing near on black wings
心臓-鐘-が行き場求め 呻き出す
My heartbeat moans like a bell, searching for a place to go
星霜の流れに隠す歪んだ思惑
Warped intentions hidden in the flow of time
艶やかに鋭い牙を剥く
Revealing gorgeously sharp fangs
巡る巡る悲劇
A tragedy that revolves and revolves
玉響に消えゆく水泡のように
Disappearing in an instant like water bubbles
儚い物語辿る運命なら
If it is fate to follow a fleeting story
曇りなき刃掲げ清い詩紡ぐ
I'll raise an unclouded blade and weave a pure song
譲れぬ未来のため
For the sake of an unyielding future
浅い眠り続く黎明に
In the dawn where shallow sleep continues
独り祈り込めて織り上げた
Woven alone, filled with prayers
涙 蒼い雲に刻まれて
Tears carved into the blue clouds
愛しあなたの影追いかける
Chasing after your beloved shadow
憎しみの炎渦巻くこの地上で
On this earth where flames of hatred swirl
汚れなき心貫いてく
Piercing through with an unblemished heart
熱き熱き誓い
A passionate, passionate vow
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Those brightly shining azure eyes
闇よりの使いに 閉ざされても
Though locked away by an agent of darkness
繋いだ夢の橋 悠久に綴りゆく
Endlessly weaving this bridge of connected dreams
奏でる 奇跡きっと...
The miracle we play, surely...
可能性の兎
[Title: The Rabbit of Possibility]
未来ある若者の芽を摘むな！
Don't nip the bud of youth with a future!
後ろ向くなお前！ 前だけ見てろ人生！
Don't look back! Look only forward in life!
ぺこちゃんのこと大好きです！
I love Pekora-chan so much!
覚醒
Awakening
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
時の鼓動がまだ響く間
While the heartbeat of time still echoes
While the pulse of time still echoes,
裸の言葉胸に閉じこめた
I locked away my unvarnished words deep in my chest.
記憶の色が滲み始める
The colors of my memories begin to blur
破れた世界の隅で
In the corner of a broken world.
何も求めずにただ抱き寄せる
Asking for nothing, I simply pull you close;
今の僕にはそれしか出来ない
That is all I am capable of doing right now.
震えた強がりでもプライドに見える
Even my trembling bluff looks like pride,
逸れた子供のように
Like a lost child.
最後の声さえも
Even my final voice
風がさまようせいで消された
Was erased by the wandering wind.
月に手を向けたまま
With hands still reached toward the moon,
君は空の星に消えた
You vanished into the stars of the sky.
『側にいて』と抱きしめても
Even if I hold you close, begging "Stay by my side,"
もう2度と聞こえない君の歌声は
Your singing voice that I can never hear again
降り注いだ雨のサイレン
Has become the siren of the pouring rain.
僕の代わりに今この空が泣き続ける
In my place, this sky continues to weep right now.
これまで踏みつけにしてきた教えを
The teachings I have trampled upon until now,
今掻き集めこの胸に当てても
Even if I gather them up and hold them to my chest,
救い求め歌うようなお遊戯に見える
It only looks like childish play, singing for salvation,
物語る大人のように
Just like adults telling stories.
言葉に寄り添うだけの
I have no need for empty love and guidance
空の愛と導きはいらない
That merely nestle up to words.
飾られた祈りでは
With an embellished prayer,
明日の手掛かりに触れない
One cannot touch a clue to tomorrow.
いつか君に届くはずの
The selfish desires drawn by a nameless, childlike poem
名も無き幼い詩が描くわがままを
That ought to reach you someday...
忘れたいよ一度だけ
I want to forget them, just this once.
眠れぬ悲しみがその詩を抱きしめてる
A sleepless sorrow holds that poem close.
Freezing cold shatters my sorrow
And scorching sand puts it together again
投げ捨てられる正しさなら
If it's a righteousness that can be thrown away,
消える事ない間違いの方のが良い
A mistake that never fades is much better.
臆病に隠してた声を今
The voice I timidly hid, now,
この手でもう一度晒せば良い
I should expose it once more with these hands.
掴む軌道も咲く光も
Both the trajectory we grasp and the blooming light
乾いた心のせいでモノクロに見えた
Seemed monochrome because of my dried-up heart.
忘れないよ今日の景色を
I won't forget the scenery of today.
ありふれた願いが足元を照らしてくれる
An ordinary wish illuminates the path beneath our feet.
Please hear me / I want to tell you
Please sing to me / I wanna hear your voice
ふぅ... ぺこーら... 一体どうなったぺこ...？
Whew... Pekora... What on earth happened, peko...?
一匹残らず...
Not a single one left...
喰らってやる！
I'll devour you all!
Crawling inside my head, shredding my self-control
It's getting close to the edge
I'm breaking down
Fragmented memories are glitching in my head
Stuck in a moment and it's burning up, bright red
A roaring howl disappears into the night
My soul is here to stay, wow wow wow wow
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity
It's changing me
My heartbeat is racing so fast, unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now, I'm just getting started, hey now
This ain't who I am, obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now, look what I've become
Obey now to me!
Your hope's gonna turn to fear
When I scream
Corrosive voices laugh and whisper in my head
Tried to ignore 'em, but they're calling for a bloodshed
I'm like a puppet, someone's pulling all the strings
Drowning in misery, I can't get out!
Breakout this rusted gate, search and eradicate, burning the hate from within
Ready to dominate
It's time to liberate
The chaos inside of him, woah woah woah
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity, straining me
My heartbeat is racing so fast, unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now, I'm just getting started, hey now
This ain't who I am, obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now, look what I've become
Obey now to me!
Your hope's gonna turn to fear
When I scream
Woah~
負けないぺこ！
I won't lose, peko!
伝説の朝に
On this legendary morning,
誓った言葉
the words we swore,
分かち合う声に
to our shared voices,
奇跡よ照らせ
may a miracle shine upon them!
革命を Let's shout
Let's shout the revolution!
風の舞うヒカリの空
Through the light-filled sky where winds dance,
吹き抜ける残響
reverberations blow through.
この右手と
With this right hand,
この左手
and this left hand,
何を求める？
what do we seek?
魂のカタルシスに
In the catharsis of the soul,
焦がれた感情
the emotions we longed for...
重ね合えば
If we overlap them,
繋ぎ合えば
if we connect them,
伝うのか？
will they reach you?
運命に委ね
Entrusting ourselves to fate,
流れのままに
going with the flow,
変わらぬビジョンじゃ
an unchanging vision...
面白くない
is no fun at all!
沸騰させよ
Boil up,
血液のレイヴ
a rave of blood!
交錯する
Intersecting,
プラズマのように
just like plasma!
革命のデュアリズム
Revolutionary Dualism,
さあ始めよう
come on, let's begin!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
Telepathic roar of life,
届いていますか？
is it reaching you?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love inherited,
ついてこい 夢の果て
follow me to the edge of dreams!
どんな人生だって
No matter what kind of life it is,
いつかは混じり合う
someday they will intertwine.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
On that day, you will make the judgment!
革命を Let's shout
Let's shout the revolution!
プラスマイナスが0の
A tuning at absolute zero,
悪くはないチューニング
isn't half bad.
キスみたいに
Like a kiss,
クラックした
cracked open,
色褪せないドリーム
a dream that never fades.
神様は希望を与え
God grants us hope,
痛みをぼかして
blurring the pain.
何を守り
What to protect,
何を信じ
what to believe,
生きろと云う？
how are we told to live?
未来への扉は
The door to the future,
コイントスさ
is a coin toss.
残酷を選べ
Choose cruelty,
暁の君
you of the dawn.
虹の架かる
Under a rainbow,
見た事ない
a never-before-seen,
絶景のフライト
stunning flight.
教えてやる
I'll show you,
覚醒のデュアリズム
the dualism of awakening.
さあ飛び込もう
Come on, let's dive in!
百花繚乱 ハウる衝動
A howling impulse in full bloom,
火花を散らして
sending sparks flying!
胸のブレイブを叩く鼓動
A heartbeat striking the courage in my chest!
どこまでいけるのか？
How far can we go?
変わらない「ナニカ」で
With an unchanging "something",
何度口づけした？
how many times have we kissed?
そして君は また恋に出会う
And so you encounter love once again.
Just trust my heart
Just feel my heart
Hold you
誇り高き愛の結晶
The crystal of prideful love,
握りしめたら 迎えにゆくから…
once you hold it tight, I'll come to get you...
刹那から一生さえ
From a single instant to a whole lifetime,
すべて見せて来た
I've shown you everything.
君へのLove song
A love song to you...
Break out! 鎖千切っテ
Break out! Break your chains,
独立セヨ
and declare independence!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
Telepathic roar of life,
届いていますか？
is it reaching you?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love inherited,
ついてこい 夢の果て
follow me to the edge of dreams!
どんな人生だって
No matter what kind of life it is,
いつかは混じり合う
someday they will intertwine.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
On that day, you will make the judgment!
革命を Let's shout
Let's shout the revolution!
ヘブンズぺこラッシュ突入ぺこ！
Heaven's Peko Rush started, peko!
撃ち抜け！
Shoot through!
スーパーヘブンズペコラッシュ 突入ペコ！
Super Heaven's Peko Rush start, peko!
I have a big gun
I took it from my Lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Have no prayer
So, I keep the gun with me
For my safety
I'll do it with no sweat
They mean business
No time for sissy pig
Queen of ocean
Sing "the Volga" to you
No need to think about it
You do it or you die
Those aren't tears
Don't let it trick on you
I am hard as steel
Get out of my way
Pay back all at once
Suck away the tender part
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
みなさん、え〜...今日は、発表があります
Everyone, um... Today, I have an announcement.
PRK48！
PRK48!
ぺこらんどむぶれいん！
Pekorandombrain!
わおっ
Wa-o!
叫んじゃえ わおっ
Shout it out, wa-o!
事件だ 毎日タイヘン
It's an incident, everyday is crazy
大成功のタネだと
Saying it's the seed for great success
笑え...泣いちゃうな 笑え！
Smile... don't cry, smile!
ぺこらった るんるんらった
Pekoratta runrun ratta
ぺこらんどむしちゃいたまえ
Please go Pekorandom
まだぺこ〜！
Not yet, peko~!
言い訳バニー
Excuses Bunny
聞きたくない言い訳バニー
Don't wanna hear it, Excuses Bunny
ジタバタの優柔不断だ
Flustered and indecisive
すぐ近くなのに 離れて感じる
Even though you're right nearby, you feel so far away.
君は バスの2つ前の席
You are two seats ahead of me on the bus.
声をかけるには ちょっと恥ずかしい
It's a bit embarrassing to speak to you.
何度 恋をしても慣れないね
No matter how many times I fall in love, I never get used to it.
カーブ曲がり 身体が傾くとき
When the bus turns a curve and our bodies tilt,
その方向は 同じさ
we lean in the exact same direction.
君に 重力シンパシー 何も 話せなくても
Gravitational sympathy with you, even if we can't speak a word,
確かに 今僕らは ひとつになる
surely right now, we are becoming one.
君に 重力シンパシー 後ろ 気づかなくても
Gravitational sympathy with you, even if you don't notice me behind you,
わかり合える日が来るよ
the day will come when we understand each other.
窓が曇るほど 乗客は多く
There are so many passengers the windows fog up,
君の 顔が陰で見えなくなる
and your face is hidden in the shadows.
喋るその声に 耳を傾けて
Listening closely to your talking voice,
僕は 胸の奥をときめかせた
my heart fluttered deep inside.
バスが急に スピード上げた瞬間
The moment the bus suddenly picked up speed,
みんな一緒に 仰け反った
everyone leaned back together.
愛は 重力フレンズ そこにいる それだけで
Love is a gravity friend, just by being there,
2人はそう 地球を共有する
the two of us share this planet Earth.
愛は 重力フレンズ 存在 認知されてなくても
Love is a gravity friend, even if my presence isn't recognized,
そのベクトル 進めばいい
it's fine to keep moving along that vector.
君に 重力シンパシー 何も 話せなくても
Gravitational sympathy with you, even if we can't speak a word,
確かに 今僕らは ひとつになる
surely right now, we are becoming one.
君に 重力シンパシー いつか 同じ重さで 愛について 想うだろう
Gravitational sympathy with you, someday with the same weight, you'll think about love.
みんな 盛り上がっていくぺこよー！
Everyone, let me hear you get hyped up, peko!
行っくよー！ お祭りだー！
Here we go! It's festival time!
乙女フェスティバル
Otome Festival!
花が咲く 夢が咲く 一度きりの物語
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom, a once-in-a-lifetime story.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって 時代を彩る Dreamer
Yamato Nadeshiko, always dreamers who color the era.
時代を彩る Dreamer
Dreamers who color the era,
無限の彼方へ
To the end of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
恋に焦がれてドキドキ
Burning with love, my heart goes pit-a-pat!
いじわるなんてイヤイヤ
Don't be mean, no, no!
とびっきりのスマイルで
With the best smile of all,
あなたを連れてったげる
I'll take you along with me.
惹かれちゃうのは運命
Falling for you is destiny!
あれもこれも抱きしめてあげる
I'll embrace all of it for you!
選ぶ道に誇りあれ
May there be pride in the path you choose.
進めば 輝く未来
If you advance, a brilliant future awaits!
乙女心 いつだってフェスティバル
A maiden's heart is always a festival!
きらめいて トキメキ届けたい 今すぐに
Sparkling, I want to deliver this excitement right now!
高く 高く そびえ立つ壁も
High, high, even towering walls,
やがて超えてくイメージだけで Let's Go! Let's Go!
just picturing us overcoming them, Let's Go! Let's Go!
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom,
一度きりの物語
a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行くさだめだから
Since it's our destiny to eventually scatter,
やるだけやるんです
we'll give it everything we've got!
笑いましょ 声高く
Let's laugh with raised voices,
明日の自分に届けたい
I want to reach my future self.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって
Yamato Nadeshiko, always,
時代を彩る Dreamer
dreamers who color the era.
無限の彼方へ
To the end of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
ワガママだっていいでしょ？
Being selfish is fine, right?
可愛いって言ってなでなで
Tell me I'm cute and pat my head!
お気に入りのスカートで
In my favorite skirt,
あなたに飛び込んでみたい
I want to jump into your arms.
夢見るだけじゃ足りない
Just dreaming isn't enough!
決める時は迷わず行きましょ
When it's time to decide, let's go without hesitation!
その手で掴む時まで
Until the moment you grasp it with those hands,
未来へ加速して行こう
let's accelerate into the future!
Destiny いつか あなたと一緒に
Destiny, someday, together with you,
永遠に触れてみたい ずっと 憧れです♪
I want to touch eternity forever, it's my dream♪
涙 はらり こぼれ落ちる日も
Even on days when tears gently fall,
本気の愛で振り向かせたい Going! Going!
I want to turn your head with true love! Going! Going!
花と舞い 夢と生き
Dancing with flowers, living with dreams,
重なり合う物語
our overlapping stories.
諦めなんて似合わないから
Because giving up doesn't suit us,
やるしかないでしょ
we just have to do it!
期待から 希望へと
From expectation to hope,
願いを鳴り響かせて
letting our wishes echo far and wide!
ヤマトナデシコ煌めいて
Yamato Nadeshiko, sparkling bright,
高鳴りを超える Future Soldier
Future Soldiers surpassing the excitement,
奇跡を信じて
believing in miracles!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
隠しきれない熱い想いと
With burning feelings that can't be hidden,
今を走れ 走れ
run through the present, run!
負けない誓い 一緒に掲げて行こう
Let's raise our unbreakable vow together and go!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う
Dancing elegantly this way and that,
予感にいざなわれ
guided by a hunch,
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
passion burns bright as we take flight!
無邪気なままじゃいられない
I can't stay innocent forever,
切り開いて見つけたいな
I want to carve a path and find it.
本当も嘘もない私になって
Becoming my true self, without truth or lies...
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom,
一度きりの物語
a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行くさだめだから
Since it's our destiny to eventually scatter,
やるだけやるんです
we'll give it everything we've got!
笑いましょ 声高く
Let's laugh with raised voices,
明日の自分に届けたい
I want to reach my future self.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって
Yamato Nadeshiko, always,
時代を彩る Dreamer
dreamers who color the era.
無限の彼方へ
To the end of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
All together! Here we go!
隠しきれない熱い想いと
With burning feelings that can't be hidden,
今を走れ 走れ
run through the present, run!
負けない誓い 一緒に掲げて行こう
Let's raise our unbreakable vow together and go!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う
Dancing elegantly this way and that,
予感にいざなわれ
guided by a hunch,
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
passion burns bright as we take flight!
大好きな歌の中なら
If it's inside the song I love so much,
声にしてもいいのぺこ...
can I express it in a voice, peko...?
思い出が強さになった
Memories turned into strength.
君となら歌えるぺこ
With you, I can sing, peko.
今日という過去が生まれて
A past called "today" is born,
未来にはどうしたいか？
and what do you want to do in the future?
描くんだ
I'll draw it out!
心からぺこらはーーー
From the bottom of her heart, Pekora...
「ありがとう」歌ってあげたいんだ
wants to sing a "thank you" to you.
始まる歌 始まる鼓動
The song begins, the pulsation starts,
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
resonate and ring out, sound of hope!
「生きる事を諦めない」と
Show that "I won't give up on living,"
示せ
Show it!
熱き夢の
The curtain rise...
幕開けを
...of a passionate dream!
爆ぜよ
Burst forth!
この
In this...
奇跡に
...miracle...
嘘はない
...there are no lies!
その手は何を掴むためにある？
What are those hands made to grasp?
たぶん待つだけじゃ叶わない
Just waiting probably won't make it come true.
その手は何を守る為にある？
What are those hands made to protect?
伝う熱は
The transmitted heat...
明日を熾す種火に
...becomes the ember to kindle tomorrow!
さあ新時代へ 銃爪を引こう
Come on, pull the trigger towards a new era!
伝説の未来へと カウントダウン
Countdown to a legendary future!
羽撃きは一人じゃない
You are not alone in flapping your wings!
過去を超えた先に
Beyond the past...
創るべき歴史が 咲き燃えてる
...the history we must create is blooming ablaze!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Unite our bonds and hearts as one,
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
resonate and ring out, sound of hope!
「信ずる事を諦めない」と
Chant, "I won't give up on believing!"
唄え
Sing!
可能性に
In possibilities...
ゼロはない
...there is no zero!
飛べよ
Fly!
この
Upon this...
奇跡に
...miracle...
光あれ
...let there be light!
切り裂け まだ見ぬ日に行く為に
Slice through to march toward days yet unseen!
不可能なんて何一つない
There is nothing impossible!
こんなに心強い事はない
Nothing could be more reassuring than this!
絶対
Absolutely...
...definitely...
絶対信じ合い
...believing in each other...
ぶっちぎる
...we'll break straight through!
例え闇に吸い込まれそうになって
Even if we feel like being swallowed by darkness,
涙さえも血に濡れて苦しくっても
and even if tears are soaked in blood and painful,
帰る場所が待っている
the place to return to is waiting!
集え
Gather!
守れ
Protect!
契れ
Pledge!
勇気の結晶が
The crystal of courage...
奇跡なんだ
...is a miracle!
願い、祈り、すべてを背負い
Carrying wishes and prayers, carrying everything,
本気を超えた本気の歌
a song of seriousness surpassing true effort!
痛みなんて何も怖くない
I'm not afraid of pain at all!
滾れ
Surge!
沸騰せよ
Boil up!
この体
This body...
穿て
Pierce through!
さあ
Now...
闇夜に
...into the dark night...
稲妻を
...strike lightning!
出会い笑い合い相手そして泣きじゃくり
Meeting, laughing together, and sobbing,
命の炎も一緒に燃やして
burning the flame of life together,
五感の全部が叫ぶ
all of my five senses cry out!
愛と
So much...
呼べる
...that it can...
ほどの
...be called love,
眩しく煌めいた
a dazzlingly sparkling...
友の証
...proof of friendship!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Unite our bonds and hearts as one...
響き
Resonate...
響き渡れ 希望の音
Resonate far and wide, sound of hope!
「信ずることを諦めない」と
"Never give up on believing,"
唄え
sing out!
可能性に
In possibilities,
ゼロはない
there is no zero.
飛べよ
Soar high,
この奇跡に光あれ
let there be light upon this miracle!
ハマードリゾートへようこそ！
Welcome to Hamado Resort!
バシバシバシバシ！ワシが行く！
Splash, splash, splash, splash! Here I go!
ハマードとはワシのことだ！
Hamado is none other than me!
みんなライブを見てくれてありぺこー！
Thank you all for watching the live stream, peko!
このあと10時15分より...
Starting after this at 10:15...
メンバーシップ限定アンコールLIVEがあるぺこ！
there'll be a members-only encore live, peko!
まだまだぺこらの新衣装見たいぺこだよね！
You still want to see more of Pekora's new outfit, right peko?
ぺこらも歌も歌いたいし、みんなに新衣装もっと見てほしい！
Pekora wants to sing more songs too, and I want everyone to see more of my new outfit!
なので是非とも遊びに来てぺこ！
So please come on over and hang out, peko!
そして、グッズのおさらいです！
And now, let's review the merch!
1つ目は、アクリルパネル！
First is the acrylic panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishの一伊那尓栖ちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
This was drawn specifically by Ninomae Ina'nis from Hololive English!
ありがとうイナちゃん！
Thank you, Ina-chan!
本当に可愛い！ぺこらかっこいいし、おしゃれだし！
It's really cute! Pekora looks so cool and stylish!
是非ともGETしてみてぺこな！
Be sure to get one, peko!
2つ目はこちら！
Second is this!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Random Acrylic Keychains!
イラストはまあるぃ先生に描いてもらいました！
The illustrations were drawn by Maarui-sensei!
いや、やっぱ最高なキーホルダー来ました、こちら！
Man, we got the most amazing keychains here!
777をやっぱ3つ揃えたいのがやっぱ人間の性なのかなー
Wanting to align all three 7s is just human nature, isn't it?
どうぺこでしょうか！
What do you think, peko?
是非とも何が届くかお楽しみに！
Please look forward to seeing which one you get!
そして3つ目は！
And third is!
ぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
Pekora's hand-written "Uso peko desho..." T-shirt!
大人気の直筆Tシャツ「うそぺこでしょ」、出ました！
The super popular hand-written T-shirt "Uso peko desho" is here!
部屋着にね、ぴったりだと思うぺこだし、
I think it's perfect as loungewear, peko,
「うそぺこでしょ」Tシャツで是非とも外にね、出かけるのも全然アリぺこだと思うので、
and wearing the "Uso peko desho" T-shirt outside is totally fine too, I think,
是非チェックしてみてください！
so please check it out!
そして4つ目は！
And fourth is!
トラックジャケット！
Track Jacket!
キービジュアルのぺこらが着ているのと同じぺこ！
It's the same one Pekora is wearing in the key visual, peko!
是非ともぺこらとお揃いで着ませんか？
Would you like to wear matching outfits with Pekora?
かっこいいしね、なんかおしゃれじゃない？
It's cool, and doesn't it look stylish?
こちらもね、コンビニ行くときでもいいし、
You can wear this when going to the convenience store,
それとも遊びに行くときでもいい、
or when going out to hang around,
部屋着にしてもいい！
or even as loungewear!
もうね、たくさん着てもらえたら嬉しいぺこなわけで、
I'd be so happy if you wear it a lot, peko,
要チェケラ！
so check it out!
そしてこちらのグッズをフルセットでご購入いただきますと、
And if you purchase the full set of these merch items,
数量限定で、ぺこらの直筆サイン＆複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる！
you'll get a limited-quantity postcard with Pekora's handwritten signature & printed message!
是非ともお手に取ってください！
Please be sure to grab one!
最高だー！
This is the best!
待っていました、この瞬間！
I've been waiting for this moment!
いいね、いいね、めちゃいいね！
Nice, nice, super nice!
熱すぎ注意！
Caution: Too hot!
オイ！オイ！オイ！
Oy! Oy! Oy!
キタ！キタ！キタ！キタ！
It's here! It's here! It's here!
たまらん！
I can't get enough!
アゲアゲ！パリナイ！
Super hyped! Party night!
来るのか？
Is it coming?
引いてしまうのか？
Am I gonna hit the jackpot?